http://www.cosn.org/privacy-policy

Jump to Navigation
Skip to Content
Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyCoSN Privacy Policy
To protect the privacy of its members and other visitors to the CoSN website, CoSN has implemented the following policies:Website
Users can visit any public web page of the CoSN website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information, however, CoSN can and may collect the following information regarding visitors to our website: domain name; user name; information regarding what pages are accessed; information volunteered by you such as survey responses or contact information; and information related to transactions such as registrations to conferences, online courses and events, and the purchase of CoSN products. CoSN may ask you to provide us with information regarding your professional interests, personal demographics, and experience with our resources. This information is collected so that we may continuously improve our products and services. Access to the Member-Only section of the CoSN website is provided through use of a login and password combination that is issued to members in good standing. Visitors seeking access to certain free materials may be asked to provide certain information about themselves as a condition of accessing that information.
If you choose to provide us with personal information such as your name and address when placing an order, registering for one of our programs or performing another task, CoSN may use that information to provide or offer you CoSN products or services, for billing purposes, to send information to you, or for other related purposes. CoSN may also share contact information with CoSN Chapter Leaders in your state so as to provide information to you from your local chapter. *For example, if you are a member, CoSN may use the information you provide us to process your application, maintain memberships, keep you abreast of latest news and programs, or respond and render services to you.
By becoming a member of CoSN, you agree to allow CoSN to include your name in our online member directory, which is accessible only to members. If you apply to become a member or are a member of any CoSN State Chapter, you have consented to the release of information related to your membership to the Chapter to which you applied.
Opting Out of the Release of Your Personal Information: Members and registered site users may opt out of receiving emails from CoSN. Please send a written request in which you identify yourself, and which clearly states your preference to opt out of receiving emails, which do include members-only benefits.
By mail:
CoSN
Attention: Opt Out
1325 G Street, NW, Suite 420
Washington, DC 20005
USA
By phone: 800.267.8747 x115
By e-mail:
Regardless of membership status, members and registered site users may also opt out of having their contact information listed in the online membership directory as well as set their own contact, address rental, and information display options in myCoSN. Log in to myCoSN at www.cosn.org and select the appropriate opt-out options.
This policy is subject to change at any time.
Content Rating
This website, as well as all websites sponsored by the Consortium for School Networking, has been rated by CoSN, based on the content rating standards of the Internet Content Rating Association. ICRA is an independent, non-profit organization with offices in the United States and Europe. The ICRA standards are designed to promote the online safety of children, while protecting the free-speech rights of content providers. Browsers can be set to bar access to those websites that include certain kinds of content that educators and parents consider to be inappropriate for children or to sites that have not rated themselves. For more information, see www.icra.org.
Accessibility
CoSN uses Bobby Worldwide software created by the Center for Applied Special Technology (CAST) to ensure its site is compliant with Section 508 and the W3C Web Accessibility Initiative. These initiatives are designed to help web page authors identify and repair significant barriers to access by individuals with disabilities, and are fully supported by CoSN.
Third-Party Ad Networks
We use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Site and on third-party websites or other media (e.g., social networking platforms). This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about you.
Users in the United States may opt out of many third-party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Consumer Choice Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by DAA companies. You may also go to the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) Consumer Opt-Out Page for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by NAI members.
Opting out from one or more companies listed on the DAA Consumer Choice Page or the NAI Consumer Opt-Out Page will opt you out from those companies’ delivery of interest-based content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Site or on other websites. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you opt out on the DAA or NAI websites, your opt-out may not be effective. Additional information is available on the DAA’s website at  www.aboutads.info or the NAI’s website at www.networkadvertising.org.
Online Behavioral Advertising and How You Can Opt-Out
We may work with third-party advertising companies who may utilize cookies and web beacons, and data collected on our services, to customize advertisements to you on our services, as well as on other websites or mobile applications in their networks beyond our services. Among other things, these customized advertisements may advertise our products and services and third party products and services on websites or mobile applications not affiliated with us. Some of these ads are online behavioral advertising – which serve advertisements that are more likely to be of interest to you using non-personal behavioral information.  Such ads may contain cookies that allow monitoring of websites and mobile applications (including our own services) and your response to such advertisements.  Cookies or web beacons placed by these companies do not collect personal information, and the third-party advertising companies do not have access to or use your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or other personal information; they may however, anonymously track your usage across our services and other websites or mobile applications in their networks. We limit companies that place our ads from using information for any purpose other than to assist us in our advertising efforts.
For more information about these third-party advertising companies' privacy policies, visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s website at https://www.networkadvertising.org. If you prefer to not receive targeted advertising, you can opt-out of network advertising programs that use your information. To do so, please visit: the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page.
Last updated: September 2020
Joining CoSN Has Its Benefits!
Discover nine ways CoSN can answer your key questions and help you transform learning in your district.
CoSN in Photos
Latest uploaded, most relevant Flickr photos
by CoSN Web 16 out of 207 on Flickr
Twitter
Got a spare hour this afternoon?
Attend @CoSN #edtechforecast event & find out how data can inform AI strategies p… https://t.co/07IFVJBjCF
RT @EdTech_K12: “There are creative approaches that districts are taking to extend their networks outside the borders of their scho… https://t.co/hpUdoOwEzy
RT @daveandcori: “There are limitations once you have all these devices out of the boundaries of your physical network,” says Amy Mc… https://t.co/L2D988S3Sf
CoSN's work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivatives 4.0 License. CoSN's logo, CETL , CTO Clinic, Peer Review, EdTechNext and CoSN Camp are registered trademarks.
Membership
Certification
Contact Us
Jobs at CoSN
Privacy Policy
Accessibility Policy
1325 G St. NW, Suite 420
Washington, DC 20005
© 2018 CoSN (Consortium for School Networking), All Rights Reserved
CLOSE MENU
Search
Main menu
AboutMembershipInstitutional MembershipCoSN + Cybersecurity CollaborativeCorporate MembershipCoSN NetworkState ChaptersVolunteerCertificationValue of the CETL®CETL® Exam and PreparationRecertificationCETL® DirectoryCertification FAQsLearningAnnual ConferenceCareer CenterNew! The CoSN PodcastCTO ClinicsCTO ForumsEarly Career K-12 CTO AcademyMicro-CredentialsOnline CoursesResource LibrarySpecial EventsWebinarsFocus AreasFramework of Essential SkillsLeadership & VisionDigital Equity InitiativeDriving K-12 InnovationEmpowered SuperintendentsGlobal LeadershipProtecting Privacy in Connected LearningResources for Rural School DistrictsState of EdTech LeadershipUnderstanding the Educational EnvironmentData-Driven Decision MakingLeadership for Digital LearningManaging Technology & Support ResourcesCybersecurityDigital AccessibilityInteroperabilityIT Crisis PreparednessSEND (Smart Education Networks by Design)Smart IT: Strategic Technology Planning & InvestmentDigital Leap Success MatrixPeer ReviewTrusted Learning Environment (TLE)Our TeamCoronavirus (COVID-19) EdTech GuidanceCorporate PartnershipsAbout CoSN AdvocacyAwardsBoard of DirectorsNews
Header Menu
Your AccountConferenceResourcesBlog
